let questions = [
    {
        numb : 1,
        question :" What is my favourite color ? ",
        answer : "Red",
        options : ["Red", "pink", "Blue", "Green"]
    },
    {
        numb : 2,
        question :" What is my favourite food ? ",
        answer : "noodles",
        options : ["chatpat", "pizza", "noodles", "laphing"]
    },
    {
        numb : 3,
        question :" What is my favourite genre ? ",
        answer : "Fantasy",
        options : ["Romance", "Fantasy", "Sci-fi", "Horror"]
    },
    {
        numb : 4,
        question :" What is my favourite social media platform ? ",
        answer : "Tiktok",
        options : ["facebook", "Instagram", "Reddit", "Tiktok"]
    },
    {
        numb : 5,
        question :" Who is my favourite superhero ? ",
        answer : "Batman",
        options : ["Superman", "Spiderman", "Batman", "Antman"]
    },
    {
        numb : 6,
        question :" What is my biggest fear ? ",
        answer : "Earthquake",
        options : ["Ghosts", "Earthquake", "Thunderstrom", "Dark"]
    },
    {
        numb : 7,
        question :" What makes me angry ? ",
        answer : "lies",
        options : ["lies", "Deception", "Bad manners", "Break up "]
    },
    {
        numb : 8,
        question :" If i can live anywhere, where would it be? ",
        answer : "NewYork",
        options : ["Los Angels", "Japan", "NewYork", "California"]
    },
    {
        numb : 9,
        question :" What would i change about myself if i could ? ",
        answer : "weight",
        options : ["weight", "face", "personality", "lips"]
    },
    {
        numb : 10,
        question :" Which is my favourite Game ? ",
        answer : "GTA series",
        options : ["GTA series", "Red Dead Redemption", "Cyberpunk", "Far Cry"]
    }
];